From 1968 til 1972, twenty-four human beings went to the moon.
Their journey lives as the ultimate adventure story.
For All Mankind is a documentary, history film directed by Al Reinert.
A testament to NASA's Apollo program of the 1960s and '70s.
Composed of actual NASA footage of the missions and astronaut interviews, the documentary offers the
viewpoint of the individuals who braved the remarkable journey to the moon and back.
Narrator - Apollo 8, Apollo 13 (voice), played by Jim Lovell.
Narrator - Apollo 9 (voice), played by Russell Schweickart.
Narrator - Apollo 10, Apollo 17 (voice), played by Eugene Cernan.
Narrator - Apollo 11 (voice), played by Michael Collins.
Narrator - Apollo 12 (voice), played by Charles Conrad.
Narrator - Apollo 12 (voice), played by Richard Gordon.
For All Mankind  is a 1987 documentary film made of original footage from NASA's Apollo program,
which successfully prepared and landed the first humans on the Moon from 1968 to 1972.
It was directed by Al Reinert, with music by Brian Eno.
The film, consisting of footage from Apollo 7 through Apollo 17, was assembled to depict what seems like a single trip to the Moon, highlighting
the beauty and otherworldliness of the images by only using audio from the interviews Reinert conducted with Apollo crew members.
The film explores themes of nasa, space mission, moon
landing, astronaut, space exploration.